<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SimpleSignIn</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In Now</string>
    <string name="enter_details_below">Enter Login Details below</string>
    <string name="sign_in_activity_email">Sign In Now</string>
    <string name="need_help">HELP</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password? Click Here</string>
    <string name="change_personal_details">Edit Details</string>
    <string name="save_personal_details">Save Changes</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Navigation View</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Navigation View Closed</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="singleton_campus_address">Swansea University Singleton Park Swansea SA2 8PP Wales, UK</string>
    <string name="bay_campus_address">Swansea University Bay Campus Fabian Way Crymlyn Burrows Swansea SA1 8EN Wales, UK</string>


    <string-array name="faq_questions">
        <item>Do I need to stay in Swansea for the exam period?</item>
        <item>What does TB1 and TB2 mean? How do I know when a class/module is taught?</item>
        <item>I am unable to attend an examination. What should I do?</item>
        <item>How does the University publish results?</item>
        <item>Will my attendance at the University be monitored?</item>
        <item>What should I do if I am unable to attend teaching sessions or examinations?</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_answers">
        <item>Semester 1 modules in Engineering, Mathematics, Biological Sciences, Computer Science, Business, Economics and Geography are all assessed by examination in January and students are required to be present for these examinations.
            Subjects outside of these areas may offer alternative assessment in Semester 1 (TB1) only.
            Students are required to speak to their home department College Office at the beginning of their period of study to enquire whether this is an option.
        </item>

        <item>TB1 = semester 1 - these modules/classes are taught in semester 1 only. Please check the module information to find out when the module/class is assessed.
            TB2 = semester 2 - these modules/classes are taught in semester 2 only and will be assessed in semester 2.
            TB1+2 = Academic year modules - these modules/classes are only available to students spending the full academic year at Swansea. Single semester students must NOT select these modules.
        </item>

        <item>
        It is essential that you inform your personal tutor or a member of the College’s administration as a matter of urgency if you are unable to attend an examination.
            If you are unable to contact a member of staff in your College you should phone the examination office on 01792 602164.
        </item>

        <item>
            You will be able to access your module marks and end of year progression decision or for final year students your award result via your intranet record on a specified date following the exam board.
            You will be sent information regarding the date of publication and instructions for accessing your result by email from the Academic Registry.
        </item>

        <item>The University monitors the attendance of students and student engagement with their programme on a regular basis.
            It does this in the student’s academic interest ensuring that the students are supported and offered advice to enable them to perform at their best.
            By monitoring student attendance the University can also identify those students who are having personal difficulties and offer appropriate advice.
            The University’s is also obliged to monitor the overseas student’s engagement with their programmes on behalf of the UKVI.
        </item>

        <item>
            The University expects students to attend every teaching session.  However if you are unable to attend you should inform your Personal Tutor.
            If you are absent for 7 days or more due to illness please also provide your College with a medical certificate.
        </item>



    </string-array>
</resources>
